<resources>
    <string name="app_name">5S Audit</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">drawer open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">drawer close</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <!--SETTINGS ACTIVITY-->
    <string name="delteAreaOk">Area was succesfully deleted</string>
    <string name="deleteTituloDialog">Delete Selected Area</string>
    <string name="elArea">The area: </string>
    <string name="deletePermanente">and related audits will be permanently deleted.</string>
    <string name="deseaContinuar">Do you wisht to continue?</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>

    <!--LOGIN ACTIVITY-->
    <string name="ingreseUsuarioValido">Please enter a valid username.</string>
    <string name="ingreseContraseniaValida">Please enter a valid password.</string>
    <string name="caracteresContrasenia">Password must be at least 6 characters</string>
    <string name="contraseniasNoCoinciden">Passwords do not match.</string>
    <string name="bienvenido">Welcome </string>
    <string name="quieroReportar">I want to report an issue</string>


    <!--enunciados-->

    <string name="enunciado11">1.1 Use of existing resources in places that are non- save locations</string>
    <string name="enunciado12">1.2 Use of existing resources in places that are to be saved</string>
    <string name="enunciado13">1.3 Conservation of facilities and resources</string>
    <string name="enunciado14">1.4 Control of conservation problems</string>
    <string name="enunciado21">2.1 Identification and signage</string>
    <string name="enunciado22">2.2 Definition and adaptation of places to store resources.</string>
    <string name="enunciado23">2.3 Order of the resources</string>
    <string name="enunciado24">2.4 Layout</string>
    <string name="enunciado31">3.1 Level of cleaning (dirt caused by people)</string>
    <string name="enunciado32">3.2 Level of cleaning (dirt caused by the process or the external spaces)</string>
    <string name="enunciado33">3.3 Cleaning standard</string>
    <string name="enunciado34">3.4 Garbage baskets And other discart collectors</string>
    <string name="enunciado41">4.1. Standardization of Paints, Identifications and Signsed
</string>;
    <string name="enunciado42">4.2. Hygiene and health
</string>;
    <string name="enunciado43">4.3. Routines and Systematics for Maintenance of 5S
</string>;
    <string name="enunciado44">4.4. Systematic of saving for electronic documents
</string>;
    <string name="enunciado51">5.1. Self-discipline in the practice of 5S
</string>;
    <string name="enunciado52">5.2. Self-discipline in compliance with rules and procedures
</string>;
    <string name="enunciado53">5.3. Attitude of people
</string>;
    <string name="enunciado54">5.4. Self-discipline in the storage of electronic documents (if any)
</string>;


    <!--criterios -->
    <!--primera s-->
    <string name="punto111">In several places, several anomalies were found in the use of resources (excessive proportions, improvisations, unnecessary resources, lack or waste)</string>
    <string name="punto112">In several places, some anomalies were found in the use of resources (excessive proportions, improvisations, unnecessary resources, lack or waste).
</string>
    <string name="punto113">In some places, several anomalies were found in the use of resources (excessive proportions, improvisations, unnecessary resources, lack or waste).</string>
    <string name="punto114">In some places, some anomalies were found in the use of resources (excessive proportions, improvisations, unnecessary resources, lack or waste).
</string>
    <string name="punto115">"every resources on floors, tables and other open space are used properly (no excess, improvisations, unnecessary resources, lack or waste).
There may be insignificant irregularities."</string>

    <string name="punto121">In several places, several anomalies were found in the use of resources (excessive proportions, improvisations, unnecessary resources, lack or waste)</string>
    <string name="punto122">In several places, some anomalies were found in the use of resources (excessive proportions, improvisations, unnecessary resources, lack or waste).</string>
    <string name="punto123">In some places, several anomalies were found in the use of resources (excessive proportions, improvisations, unnecessary resources, lack or waste).</string>
    <string name="punto124">In some places, some anomalies were found in the use of resources (excessive proportions, improvisations, unnecessary resources, lack or waste).</string>
    <string name="punto125">"Every resources in closets, drawers and other enclosed spaces are shared and used correctly  (no excess, improvisations, unnecessary resources, lack or waste).
There may be insignificant irregularities.</string>

    <string name="punto131">There are widespread conservation problems and some compromise the safety or functionality of facilities and resources, according to environmental characteristics.</string>
    <string name="punto133">There are conservation problems in some facilities or resource. some compromises the safety or functionality, according to environmental characteristics.</string>
    <string name="punto132">There are widespread conservation problems but not compromise the safety or functionality of facilities and resources, according to environmental characteristics.</string>
    <string name="punto134">There are conservation problems in some facilities or resource but not compromises the safety or functionality, according to environmental characteristics.</string>
    <string name="punto135">All facilities and resources are in good condition. There may be insignificant irregularities for the characteristics of the environment.</string>

    <string name="punto141">There is no formal justification for most conservation problems encountered</string>
    <string name="punto142">There is no formal justification for some conservation problems, including for some that compromises the safety or functionality of facilities and resources, according to environmental characteristics.</string>
    <string name="punto143">There is no formal justification for some conservation problems, but it does not compromises the safety or functionality of facilities and resources, according to environmental characteristics.</string>
    <string name="punto144">There is no formal justification for one conservation problem, but it does not compromis the safety or functionality of facilities and resources, according to environmental characteristics.</string>
    <string name="punto145">There is a formal justification for all conservation problems and none of them compromise the safety or functionality of facilities and resources. There may be insignificant irregularities for the characteristics of the environment.</string>

    <!--segunda s-->
    <string name="punto211">In several places there are deficiencies of identification and signaling. There is no plan for the correction of most of the deficiences</string>
    <string name="punto212">In several places there are deficiencies of identification and signaling. There is no plan for the correction some of them.</string>
    <string name="punto213">In some places there are deficiencies of identification and signaling. There is no plan for the correction some of them.</string>
    <string name="punto214">In some places there are deficiencies of identification and signaling. There is a plan for the correction of them</string>
    <string name="punto215">In all places there are identifications and signage  that facilitate the location and avoid the loss of time and risks. There may be insignificant irregularities for the characteristics of the environment.</string>

    <string name="punto221">In several places there are several resources without defined  and suitable places for their storage (format, dimensions, type of material, etc.).</string>
    <string name="punto222">In several places there are some resources without defined  and suitable places for their storage (format, dimensions, type of material, etc.).</string>
    <string name="punto223">In some places there are several resources without defined  and suitable places for their storage (format, dimensions, type of material, etc.).</string>
    <string name="punto224">In some places there are some resources without defined  and suitable places for their storage (format, dimensions, type of material, etc.).</string>
    <string name="punto225">There are defined and suitable places for all the resources used (format, dimensions, type of material, etc.). There may be insignificant irregularities for the characteristics of the environment.</string>

    <string name="punto231">In several places were found several resources disordered, making access difficult (there are useful resources outside the places of store, mixture, difficulty of visual identification or risk problems).</string>
    <string name="punto232">In several places were found some resources disordered, making access difficult (there are useful resources outside the places of store, mixture, difficulty of visual identification or risk problems).</string>
    <string name="punto233">In some places were found several resources disordered, making access difficult (there are useful resources outside the places of store, mixture, difficulty of visual identification or risk problems).</string>
    <string name="punto234">In some places were found some resources disordered, making access difficult (there are useful resources outside the places of store, mixture, difficulty of visual identification or risk problems).</string>
    <string name="punto235">All resources are classified and organized (there are no resources available outside of storage places, mixed, difficulty of visual location or risk problems).There may be insignificant irregularities for the characteristics of the environment.</string>

    <string name="punto241">In several places there are design deficiencies that promote fatigue, risks and lost time (planned distribution of productive and / or support resources, hampering circulation and access, incompatible space or volume, etc.). There is no plan for the correction of the majority.</string>
    <string name="punto242">In several places there are design deficiencies that promote fatigue, risks and lost time (planned distribution of productive and / or support resources, hampering circulation and access, incompatible space or volume, etc.). There is no plan for the correction some of them.</string>
    <string name="punto243">In some places there are design deficiencies that promote fatigue, risks and lost time (planned distribution of productive and / or support resources, hampering circulation and access, incompatible space or volume, etc.). There is no plan for the correction some of them.</string>
    <string name="punto244">In some places there are design deficiencies that promote fatigue, risks and lost time (planned distribution of productive and / or support resources, hampering circulation and access, incompatible space or volume, etc.). There is a plan for the correction of them</string>
    <string name="punto245">The location of all productive and support resources is appropriate, facilitates movement and / or access, avoiding risks, fatigue and loss of time. It may have insignificant irregularities for the characteristics of the environment.</string>

    <!--tercera s-->
    <string name="punto311">In several places there is dirt, all caused by the people of the area</string>
    <string name="punto312">In several places there is  dirt, some provoked by the people of the area or by non compliance with the cleaning routine.</string>
    <string name="punto313">In some places there is  dirt, some provoked by the people of the area or by non compliance with the cleaning routine.</string>
    <string name="punto314">In some places there is dirt clearly provoked by people from other areas or simply by non compliance with the cleaning routine.</string>
    <string name="punto315">There is no dirt caused by people or lack of cleaning routine. There may be insignificant irregularities for the characteristics of the environment.</string>

    <string name="punto321">In several places there are source of dirt or accumulation of dirt of long time, generating risks of accidents and that are not contained.</string>
    <string name="punto322">In some places there are source of dirt or accumulation of dirt of long time, generating risks of accidents and that are not contained.</string>
    <string name="punto323">The sources of dirt or accumulation of dirt of long time, is not generating risks of accidents. There is no defined deadline for the removal of sources of dirt.</string>
    <string name="punto324">The sources of dirt or accumulation of dirt of long time, is not generating risks of accidents. There is defined deadline for the removal of sources of dirt.</string>
    <string name="punto325">Sources of dirt (machinery, equipment, handling of product) or dirt accumulated over time do not create a risk of accidents and the extinction of their source was considered technically and financially unviable by the company. There may be insignificant irregularities for the characteristics of the environment.</string>

    <string name="punto331">There is no defined frequency and / or suitable for cleaning any type of dirt (generated by processes, handing of product,  weather, animals, trees, transport, etc.).</string>
    <string name="punto332">There is no defined frequency and / or suitable for cleaning several type of dirt (generated by processes, handing of product,  weather, animals, trees, transport, etc.).</string>
    <string name="punto333">There is no defined frequency and / or suitable for cleaning some type of dirt (generated by processes, handing of product,  weather, animals, trees, transport, etc.).</string>
    <string name="punto334">There is a defined frequency and suitable for cleaning all type of dirt (generated by processes, handing of product,  weather, animals, trees, transport, etc.).The systematic does not include, in writing, all places of difficult access.</string>
    <string name="punto335"> There is a defined frequency and suitable for cleaning all type of dirt (generated by processes, handing of product,  weather, animals, trees, transport, etc.). The routine  includes, all the places of difficult access.</string>
    <string name="punto341">In several places there are several deficiencies in waste baskets, and other collectors  (quantity, identification, conservation, hygiene, size, cleaning frequency, identification, signaling, practice of selective collection, etc.).</string>
    <string name="punto342">In several places there are some deficiencies in waste baskets, and other collectors  (quantity, identification, conservation, hygiene, size, cleaning frequency, identification, signaling, practice of selective collection, etc.).</string>
    <string name="punto343">In some places there are several deficiencies in waste baskets, and other collectors  (quantity, identification, conservation, hygiene, size, cleaning frequency, identification, signaling, practice of selective collection, etc.).</string>
    <string name="punto344">In some places there are some deficiencies in waste baskets, and other collectors  (quantity, identification, conservation, hygiene, size, cleaning frequency, identification, signaling, practice of selective collection, etc.).</string>
    <string name="punto345">All waste baskets, and other collectors are suitable  (quantity, identification, conservation, hygiene, size, cleaning frequency, identification, signaling, practice of selective collection, etc.). There may be insignificant irregularities for the characteristics of the environment.</string>
    <string name="verCriterios">Criteria</string>
    <string name="criteriaTitulo">Criteria</string>
    <string name="sacarFoto">Add photo</string>
    <string name="guardarAuditoria">Save Audit</string>
    <string name="salir">Quit</string>
    <string name="manageAreas">Manage audit areas</string>
    <string name="myAudits">MY AUDITS</string>
    <string name="addNewArea">Add new Area</string>
    <string name="generarPDF">Send PDF report</string>
    <string name="quit">Quit</string>
    <string name="signOut">Log out</string>
    <string name="settings">SETTINGS</string>

    <string name="punto411">There are only a few rules on identifications and signage. Most do not obey any rules.</string>
    <string name="punto412">There are some rules on identifications and signage. Most do not obey any standard.
</string>
    <string name="punto413">In all places there are identifications and signage. There may be some insignificant irregularity for the characteristics of the environment. Some paintings, identifications and signage do not obey a standard.
</string>
    <string name="punto414">In all places there are identifications and signage. There may be some insignificant irregularity for the characteristics of the environment. Few paintings, identifications and signage do not obey a standard.
</string>
    <string name="punto415">In all places there are identifications and signage. There may be an insignificant irregularity for the characteristics of the environment. All paintings, identifications and signage are standardized.
</string>
    <string name="punto421">There are some ergonomic problems and / or some hygiene problems in the work area, but there is no plan to solve it
</string>
    <string name="punto422">There are some ergonomic problem and / or  hygiene problem in the work area, but there is no study to solve them.
</string>
    <string name="punto423">There are some ergonomic problem and / or hygiene problem in the work area and there is study to solve them.
</string>
    <string name="punto424">There are some ergonomic problem and / or hygiene problem in the work area and there are concrete actions to solve it.
</string>
    <string name="punto425">There is no ergonomic or hygiene problem in the work area It may have insignificant irregularities for the characteristics of the environment.
</string>
    <string name="punto431">There is no system for maintenance of 5S. The practice is random.
</string>
    <string name="punto432">There is some system for maintenance to 5S, but it does not guarantee continuous improvement (evaluations, action plans, division of responsibilities, disclosure of rules, meetings, recognition, disclosure of results, etc.)
</string>
    <string name="punto433">There is a system for continuous improvement of 5S, but there is a deficiency in several aspects  (evaluations, action plans, division of responsibilities, disclosure of rules, meetings, recognition, disclosure of results, etc.)
</string>
    <string name="punto434">There is a system for continuous improvement of 5S, but there is a deficiency in some aspects  (evaluations, action plans, division of responsibilities, disclosure of rules, meetings, recognition, disclosure of results, etc.)
</string>
    <string name="punto435">There is an efficient system for the continuous improvement of 5S  (evaluations, action plans, division of responsibilities, disclosure of rules, meetings, recognition, disclosure of results, etc.)
</string>
    <string name="punto441">There is no defined criteria for the electronic storage of documents.
</string>
    <string name="punto442">The possible definition for the electronic storage of documents  is not extended for all types (Net, CPU, E-mail).
</string>
    <string name="punto443">There is no defined protocol for the storage of electronic documents. (Net, CPU, E-mail). Some folders and shared files do not uniform denomination.
</string>
    <string name="punto444">There is defined  for the storage  of electronic documents (Net, CPU, E-mail).  There is no clear separation beetwen a personal and profesional files.
</string>
    <string name="punto445">There is a definition for keeping all types of electronic documents (network, CPU, E-mail). All shared files and folders have uniform names. There is a general separation beetwen of personal and profesional  files. There may be insignificant irregularities for the characteristics of the environment.
</string>

    <string name="punto511">Some of the people observed / interviewed, practice 5S in the day to day without need of monitoring or order
</string>
    <string name="punto512">several of the people observed / interviewed, practice 5S in the day to day without need of monitoring or order
</string>
    <string name="punto513">Some of the people observed / interviewed, do not practice 5S in the day to day without need of monitoring or order
</string>
    <string name="punto514">Few of the people observed / interviewed, do not practice 5S in the day to day without need of monitoring or order
</string>
    <string name="punto515">"All of people observed / interviewed, practice 5S in the day to day without need of monitoring or order
Even in other areas that they frequent or work.
"
</string>
    <string name="punto521">some of the people observed / interviewed comply with norms, rules and procedures (safety, environment, quality, etc.), without the need for monitoring or order
</string>
    <string name="punto522">several of the people observed / interviewed comply with norms, rules and procedures (safety, environment, quality, etc.), without the need for monitoring or order
</string>
    <string name="punto523">some of the people observed / interviewed do not comply with norms, rules and procedures (safety, environment, quality, etc.), without the need for monitoring or order
</string>
    <string name="punto524">Few of the people observed / interviewed do not comply with norms, rules and procedures (safety, environment, quality, etc.), without the need for monitoring or order
</string>
    <string name="punto525">All of people observed / interviewed do not comply with norms, rules and procedures (safety, environment, quality, etc.), without the need for monitoring or order
</string>
    <string name="punto531">"Most people observed / interviewed have problems, such as: * Inappropriate behavior in their area or in the area of others
* Inadequate material displayed in the workplace (adhesives, obscene photos, graffiti, etc.)
* Inadequate use of collective spaces (water, energy, bathroom, copier, coffee, etc.).
* Inadequate smoking practice
* Lack of team spirit
* Lack of initiative for 5S, etc.."
</string>
    <string name="punto532">"Several people observed / interviewed have problems, such as: * Inappropriate behavior in their area or in the area of others
* Inadequate material displayed in the workplace (adhesives, obscene photos, graffiti, etc.)
* Inadequate use of collective spaces (water, energy, bathroom, copier, coffee, etc.).
* Inadequate smoking practice
* Lack of team spirit
* Lack of initiative for 5S, etc.."
</string>
    <string name="punto533">"Some people observed / interviewed have problems, such as: * Inappropriate behavior in their area or in the area of others
* Inadequate material displayed in the workplace (adhesives, obscene photos, graffiti, etc.)
* Inadequate use of collective spaces (water, energy, bathroom, copier, coffee, etc.).
* Inadequate smoking practice
* Lack of team spirit
* Lack of initiative for 5S, etc.."
</string>
    <string name="punto534">"Few people observed / interviewed have problems, such as: * Inappropriate behavior in their area or in the area of others
* Inadequate material displayed in the workplace (adhesives, obscene photos, graffiti, etc.)
* Inadequate use of collective spaces (water, energy, bathroom, copier, coffee, etc.).
* Inadequate smoking practice
* Lack of team spirit
* Lack of initiative for 5S, etc.."
</string>
    <string name="punto535">"Non of the people observed / interviewed have problems, such as: * Inappropriate behavior in their area or in the area of others
* Inadequate material displayed in the workplace (adhesives, obscene photos, graffiti, etc.)
* Inadequate use of collective spaces (water, energy, bathroom, copier, coffee, etc.).
* Inadequate smoking practice
* Lack of team spirit
* Lack of initiative for 5S, etc.."</string>
    <string name="punto541">There are several anomalies in the storage of various types of electronic documents (obsolete, mixed personal and profesional documents, documents outside the specific directory / file, file names, outside the established standard, etc.).</string>
    <string name="punto542">There are several anomalies in the storage of some types of electronic documents (obsolete, mixed personal and profesional documents, documents outside the specific directory / file, file names outside the established standard, etc.).</string>
    <string name="punto543">There are some anomalies in the storage of various types of electronic documents (obsolete, mixed personal and profesional documents, documents outside the specific directory / file, file names outside the established standard, etc.).</string>
    <string name="punto544">There are some anomalies in the storage of some types of electronic documents (obsolete, mixed personal and profesional documents, documents outside the specific directory / file, file names outside the established standard, etc.).</string>
    <string name="punto545">All electronic documents are used and stored in appropriate folders in accordance with the established standard. It may have insignificant irregularities for the characteristics of the environment.</string>
    <string name="sinAreas">No areas created. Go to \"Settings\" menu and then click \"Manage audit areas\"</string>
    <string name="verAuditoria">Audit detail</string>
    <string name="start">START AUDIT</string>
    <string name="contact">CONTACT US</string>
    <string name="firstTime">First time? Click here</string>
    <string name="autenticacionFallida">Authentication Failed. Please register.</string>
    <string name="sinConexionIntenteMasTarde">No internet connections, please try again later.</string>
    <string name="reporteAuditoria">Audit report.</string>
    <string name="enviarMail">Send mail.</string>
    <string name="errorRevisarPermisos">Error, check permissions.</string>
    <string name="tituloPdf">5S Audit Report</string>
    <string name="ResultadoFinal">Final result.</string>
    <string name="puntajeFinal">Final score:</string>
    <string name="fecha">Date:</string>
    <string name="score">Score:</string>
    <string name="detalleAuditoria">Audit detail</string>
    <string name="misAuditorias">My audits</string>
    <string name="textoIssue">Please, tell us if you had any problem using our App. Suggestions are also welcome!</string>
    <string name="audit5s">5S Audit</string>
    <string name="agregarComentario">Add a comment</string>
    <string name="favorAgregueComentario">Please, add a comment for this photo</string>
    <string name="comment">comment</string>
    <string name="advertencia">Warning!</string>
    <string name="auditoriaSinTerminar">The audit is not finished.</string>
    <string name="continuar">Continue?</string>
    <string name="si">Yes</string>
    <string name="seiriSeiri">Seiri / Sort</string>
    <string name="seitonSeiton">Seiton / Set in order</string>
    <string name="seisoSeiso">Seiso / Shine</string>
    <string name="seiketsuSeiketsu">Seiketsu / Standarize</string>
    <string name="shitsukeShitsuke">Shitsuke / Sustain</string>
    <string name="noEncontroDatos">No data found</string>
    <string name="dismiss">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="appNecesitaPermiso">App needs permission to store audit data</string>
    <string name="damePermiso">Please grant storage permissions to take photos</string>
    <string name="completarItemFaltante">You must complete items:</string>
    <string name="avisoSignout">You are about to log out your account.</string>
    <string name="databaseDelete">Delete database</string>
    <string name="auditsWillBeDeleted">All your Audits will be permanently deleted</string>
    <string name="confirmaBorrarBaseDeDato">All data was successfully deleted</string>
    <string name="selectArea">Select area</string>
    <string name="audit">Audit</string>
    <string name="target">Target</string>
    <string name="seleccionaImagen">Choose image</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="permisoParaFotos">Please grant storage permissions to take photos</string>
    <string name="noSeCreoDirectorio">The requested Directory was not created.</string>
    <string name="nombreArea">Insert new area name:</string>
    <string name="areaName">area name</string>
    <string name="creadoExitosamente"> was successfuly created</string>
    <string name="auditResult">Audit result</string>
    <string name="bad">Bad</string>
    <string name="average">Average</string>
    <string name="good">Good</string>
    <string name="auditResultFor">Audit Result for:</string>
    <string name="titulo">Title:</string>
    <string name="manageAuditAreas">Manage Audit Areas</string>
    <string name="databaseAuditDelete">delete data</string>
    <string name="goBack">Go back</string>
    <string name="enunciado">Statement</string>
    <string name="clicToAddComment">Click here to add comment</string>
    <string name="e5s">e-5S</string>
    <string name="mail">mail</string>
    <string name="hinPass">password</string>
    <string name="signIn">Sign in</string>
    <string name="register">register</string>
    <string name="disclaimer">Please register. an Email address is required for authentication. Your data will not be used for any other purpose</string>
    <string name="auditResult1">Audit.</string>
    <string name="version" translatable="false">v1.0.10</string>
    <string name="tutorial_tit_setting">Before starting to audit</string>
    <string name="tutorial_desc_setting">First, we need to create an auditable area. Lets go to settings</string>
    <string name="verTutorial">Thank you for downloading our app.\nDo you want to see a quick tutorial?</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="tutorial_tit_area">Manage audit areas</string>
    <string name="tutorial_desc_area">Click here to add or remove audit areas</string>
    <string name="tutorial_desc_manage">Click here to add an area, to remove an area, click the red cross next to it.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_tit_manage">Add an audit area</string>
    <string name="tutorial_tit_graficos_ver">Check audit details.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_desc_graficos_ver">Click here to see audit score and photos.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_tit_graficos_pdf">Send PDF report.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_desc_graficos_pdf">Click here to send a PDF report, with scores, photos and comments. You can use any of your mail accounts.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_tit_subitem_general">Let\'s get started</string>
    <string name="tutorial_desc_subitem_general">You are ready to audit! choose an area.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_tit_subitem_criteria">Check criteria.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_desc_subitem_criteria">If you are not sure on how to score, you can always check criteria. you will find useful guidelines.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_tit_subitem_foto">Take some photos</string>
    <string name="tutorial_desc_subitem_foto">Add photos and comments on your findings.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="tutorial_tit_strt">Start auditing</string>
    <string name="tutorial_desc_strt">Pick an audit area, and start auditing right now.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_tit_logout">Log out your account.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_desc_logout">Click here if you want to logout your account or sign in with a different username.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_tit_delete">Delete all data</string>
    <string name="tutorial_desc_delete">Click here if you want to remove all data. all areas and audits will be deleted.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_tit_guardar">Save your audit</string>
    <string name="tutorial_desc_guardar">Once you have finished the audit save it and proceed to results.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_tit_navegar">Navigate through the audit.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_desc_navegar">Click here to navigate through the audit, or simply swipe the screen.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_tit_subitem_inicial">Start audit.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_desc_subitem_inicial">Read the statement and score taking criteria into account.</string>
    <string name="noHayInternet">Internet connection needed to register new users</string>
    <string name="noHayInternetlogin">Internet connection needed for first login</string>
    <string name="reintentar">Retry</string>
    <string name="activarTuto">Turn tutorial on</string>
    <string name="desactivarTuto">Turn tutorial off</string>
    <string name="tutorial_tit_tuto">Tutorial</string>
    <string name="tutorial_desc_tuto">Click here to turn on and off the tutorial.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_tit_search">Browse your audits</string>
    <string name="tutorial_desc_search">Click here to browse your audits.</string>
    <string name="deleteAudit">Delete audit</string>
    <string name="auditoriaSeEliminara">The audit will be deleted.</string>
    <string name="titNoMemoria">No storage found</string>
    <string name="noMemoria">Storage unavailable. Please insert an SD card or disconnect your device from computer.</string>
    <string name="guardardar">Do you want to save before quitting?</string>
    <string name="usuarioRepetido">User with this email already exists.</string>
    <string name="datosErroneos">Wrong password</string>
    <string name="forgot">Forgot password?</string>
    <string name="noMail">Please enter a valid email to reset your password</string>
    <string name="mailReestablecimientoEnviado">Instructions sent to: </string>
    <string name="mailVerificacionEnviado">Verification mail sent to:</string>
    <string name="errorMailVerificacion">Verification mail was not send. Check connection.</string>
    <string name="titNoVerificado">Unverified user</string>
    <string name="descNoVerificado">is not verified. if you want us to resend rverification mail click \"Resend\"</string>
    <string name="resend">Resend</string>
    <string name="later">Later</string>
    <string name="loginVerificado">I\'ve done it</string>
    <string name="mailReestablecerError">Instructios could not be sent. Check your connection.</string>
    <string name="verPass">Show password</string>
    <string name="passwordOlvidada">Password recovery</string>
    <string name="enviaremosInstrucciones">We will send a password recovery mail to:</string>


</resources>
